Title: Live Content

Description: Fetched live

Source: https://sheshyguides.blogspot.com/2021/06/mod-guide.html

---
Mod Guide
Skip to main content
Search This Blog
Miner Gun Builder Guides
Mod Guide
Get link
Facebook
X
Pinterest
Email
Other Apps
June 26, 2021
Here's a guide for all the mods in the game. I realize this doesn't include all interactions and skills, but I hope it helps!
Turns path in ship to the right. With the skill, it's best to put non-damage mods as early in the path as possible, as this mod will add flat damage.
Turns path in ship to the left.
+1 damage. With the second skill, the damage increase from this mod becomes polynomial, but is inferior to other damage mods.
+1 bullet speed. Using too many of this mod will make some bullets phase through blocks.
Bullets fire in a random direction towards the left up to ~45 degrees. Using multiple forces the spread further to the side.
Bullets fire in a random direction up to ~45 degrees to either side. Using multiple increases the angle the bullets spread.
Bullets fire in a random direction towards the right up to ~45 degrees.
Bullets fire in a random direction up to ~30 degrees to either side. Using multiple increases the angle the bullets spread.
Bullets curve to the left. Curve is not random. Using multiple tightens the angle of the curve.
Bullets fire with a random curve. Using multiple gives the possibility of tighter curves. This effectively increases the width of the angle the bullets eject at.
Bullets curve to the right.
Divides bullet speed by 2.
33% chance for 2X damage.
4% chance for 10X damage.
Picks a random multiplier out of 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,2,3,4. When it picks 0, the bullet is deleted.
This mod has a stored value. When a bullet passes through, the bullet adds 20% of its damage to the stored value, without removing damage from the bullet. Then, the same bullet receives 10% of the stored value. This happens again for every bullet that passes through.
Bullet turns 180 degrees after hitting a block. Using multiple of this mod allows bullets to bounce multiple times.
Bullet bounces in a random direction after hitting a block. Using multiple of this mod allows bullets to bounce multiple times.
Bullet bounces at the angle it realistically would. This mod does take corners of blocks into account when calculating the angle to bounce at. Using multiple of this mod allows bullets to bounce multiple times.
Doubles lifetime of the projectile. Useful when using slow projectiles or for waves.
Left and right turn in one mod. This splits the path into two directions, cloning the projectiles that pass through. This does NOT divide the damage between the paths.
Same as previous, but with an additional forward path.
Randomly chooses between a left and right turn, and gives bullet 2X damage.
Randomly chooses between left, straight, or right, and gives bullet 3X damage.
Bullets retain 20%? of their damage after destroying a block. Applies through multiple blocks if damage is high enough. Using multiple increases amount of damage retained after piercing.
Bullets pierce through an additional block. Using multiple pierces through multiple blocks.
Applies a circular shaped AOE to bullet after hitting a block. Using multiple increases the size of the AOE.
Applies a sideways AOE to bullet after hitting a block. Using multiple increases the size of the AOE.
Bullets move towards each other after firing. Using multiple increases the attraction.
"Bullets align their direction." Takes the average angle of bullets on screen and applies this average to each bullet. Change in direction is gradual. Using multiple changes the angle faster.
Bullets move towards a line in front of the ship. Using multiple increases attraction to front of ship.
+1 bullet. Adds a bullet for every parent projectile that passes through. The new bullet is not counted as a parent projectile, but keeps all the stats of the original bullet.
Redirects all bullets forwards after traveling a short and random distance. Using multiple increases the distance traveled before redirecting forwards.
Sends bullets left or right after traveling a short distance. Direction and distance is random. Using multiple increases the distance traveled before projectiles turn.
30% increase to money gained. Path must enter through side first, then through the back.
Saves damage from the bullet when the path enters either side. When the same path enters the back, the saved damage is added.
Gives tier/10 rounded down as damage. Its use depends on your other sources of flat damage. If you have low base damage, this mod is incredibly powerful. Best to place this and other flat damage mods at the beginning of the path.
Increases visual size and hitbox size of bullets, and gives 2X damage. This mod is a good addition to any build, because of the damage increase. The size increase can also be used to make hitting side by side blocks at the same time easier.
2X damage in the last 0.4 seconds of a bullet's life. Especially with its skills, this mod can give a lot of damage, but is incredibly hard to use. With achievements, base lifetime is 4 seconds. This means that the effect is only active in the last 10% of a bullet's life (without skills).
Each empty tiles gives 10% more damage. Heavily depends on the build you use and what skills you have. Without skills, it's usually useless. With skills, it can easily give over 3X damage.
Deals more damage the slower your bullet travels, up to 5X damage. Really powerful if you can get your bullets slow enough, but it would take a lot of mods spaces to do so.
Combines 10 bullets into 1 and gives 2X damage. The damage buff is really nice, but the reduction in projectiles can be restrictive.
Changes direction every 0.2 seconds. Each direction change increases damage slightly. This buff starts at 5%, but goes down with every direction change.
Any turn that comes after this mod becomes a 1.1X multiplier. It's best to put this mod before all turns. This mod doesn't do anything at the mod, so it doesn't matter if it goes before flat damage, but flat damage should still go before turns if possible.
Adds 100 damage. This mod can be useful when first unlocked, but is generally inferior to the other 2 flat damage legendary mods.
Gives 10 damage for each unused ejection block. Multiple sides of one ejection block can be used without reducing damage received from this mod. With the skill and depending on the ship, this mod can give over 300 damage.
X2 damage when there are 10 or fewer bullets on screen. No damage buff with 11 or more bullets on screen. Multiplier is calculated at mod, not at ejection.
Duplicates every bullet that passes through, including parent projectiles. Placement relative to +1 projectile mods does not matter.
Get link
Facebook
X
Pinterest
Email
Other Apps
Comments
Post a Comment
Popular posts from this blog
Ship Builds
June 26, 2021
This is a list of ship builds with their costs. These builds are not meant to be optimized builds, but ones that should be easily attainable from the previous one in progressing through the game. Feel free to skip buying ships, as this will likely save time. These builds are also ignoring alliance buffs. Rider-Used Build cost: 30, but given through tutorial Rider Build cost: 50 for ship, 60 for mods, 140 total Transporter Build cost: 150 for ship, 220 for mods, 460 total Rocket Build cost: 600 for ship, 320 for mods, 1230 total Alien Seeker Build cost: 1500 for ship, 0 for mods, 2130 total Bus Build cost: 3500 for ship, 2540 for mods, 6670 total Capable of 480 damage in a single bullet. This ship will get you to 3 base damage with achievements. Fighter Build cost: 7000 for ship, 2100 for mods, 12270 total With 3 base damage, you should start moving away from +1 damage mods now. Family Cruiser I don't recommend buying this ship. Two ejectors with 4.5 firerate is good at this point,...
Read more
Meta Paths
June 29, 2021
Here's a list of the best paths I have found for every pre-built ship in the game. Many of these paths aren't usable when you first obtain the ship, as they may take too many turns. Some paths will depend on whether or not you have you damage cross skill or not, and which legendary mods you use.� I will not be including ships with only one path. If you find a significantly better path for any ship, I will replace it with yours and list your name if desired.
Read more
Early Custom Builds
July 01, 2021
These are the custom ship builds I used in my second play-through. These are not necessarily optimized builds, but the way I like to start waves. I recommend getting to tier 1000 before starting waves. I don't recommend farming with this build or any ship with only one chunk purchased, unless you are really bored with farming wave 1 over and over. Even then, any build with one chunk is not going to be amazing. I really like using speed chunks, as they are easy to path and make farming RC much faster. The chunk that gives a 5% chance for RC is also a good option starting out, but is not as good late into waves and does not usually give as many mods. Added another speed chunk, which added 6 mods spaces. You'll quickly see that stacking square AOE is one of the fastest ways to clear waves. If you stack 10 of them, you'll hit the whole width of the blocks. Doing more damage will eventually be very important, but for now the tier damage mod will give you plenty. You guessed it!...
Read more
Powered by Blogger
Theme images by
Radius Images
Sheshy
Visit profile
Archive
July 2021
1
June 2021
5
Report Abuse
